Good Morning
Good morning
This is Tentavi.
Yes, Tentavistart.
We're off to a lukewarm start.
Good morning.
I came outside.
The weather... I heard it was going to rain today.
It's so sunny.
It's sunny.
It's nice.
Wow, it's a bright pool.
Yesterday was a night pool.
That was fun. Yeah, it was fun.
Did you guys see that?
They're having a blast, so, yeah.
I wanna go in the freezer.
They said it starts at 9:00. 9:00? What time is it?
It's a little early, like 7:00 or something.
Not yet. - 9:00.
Not yet. But the ocean is holding today, so yes, it is.
I'm so excited! Yay!
Yeah, the ocean.
It's gonna be fun. It's gonna be fun.
It's beautiful. Here we go.
Look at that!
It's so beautiful.
How's it look? Good?
It looks good.
Look at the sky.
There it is.
It's so beautiful!
There's a rainbow.
Where? There it is.
Can you see it?
Maybe there's a reflection.
There's a rainbow.
It's right here.
What? I don't know.
It's so thin.
Wow, that's amazing.
I heard you can reach the ocean from here.
Is it this way?
This way?
Oh, wow, but...
Wow.
Ta-da!
It's so bright.
It's bright, but...
Beautiful.
Oh, my God.
Wow, it's great!
That's great.
I like this kind of thing.
Aren't the stars so beautiful?Aren't the stars beautiful?
I was in Aspazanio.
What?
I know you and Ken are good friends.
You know, the other day...
He told me to take care of Saku.
We've never met before.
Nice to meet you.
Tell him I'm his mom, too.
I told her.
What time do you leave?
Twenty.
I'll be there.
Wow, it's so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
All right.
Bon appétit.
Ta-da!
Oh, my gosh!
It looked so good.
It looked so good!
It's hard to decide what to eat at such a buffet!
It's beautiful. It looks like a composite.
Really. A composite background?
It's a composite, right?
Composite.
You didn't pick okra today?
No, I didn't pick okra today.I didn't take it today.
Tomatoes.
Yes, I did.
I picked them.
Yes, it's good.
Delicious.
It's delicious.
I stayed up late last night.
It's true.
Today is an elegant morning
Elegant morning.
But only hours ago.
Yes, really
Hours ago.
You know...
I was kind of lazy.
But I think I slept relatively well.
But did I hear you talking in your sleep?
No!
I heard she talks a lot in her sleep.
Really?
For a long time.
In the middle of the night.
Yeah, I think he woke up once.
When your sister popped out.
What? What is it? She said...
I thought I heard you.
I think I heard her.I think I heard you.
I don't think so.
What? What is it? I thought...
I thought maybe you were awake.
I could sleep.
I thought you were talking too long.
You're so cute.
Oh, my God, he heard me.
I fell asleep.
I heard White talks a lot.
Oh, really?
But Soku-chan with glasses...
I don't like it.
Do you know him? They don't know.
I don't know.
I thought it was unusual.
Yeah, it's rare.
How unusual?
Yeah, it is.
I wear contacts even when I leave the house.
I definitely wear them when I go out.
Glasses. It's not that easy.
Don't tell anyone.
Cut.
I'm going to the beach.
Rain is in the forecast. I'm sure of it.
It's getting a little cloudy.
It's raining.
It's starting to rain.It's raining.
I don't know if I'm a sunny girl or a rainy girl.
It's starting to rain.
It's raining a lot.
It's raining so hard!
It's amazing!
Squalls.
It's amazing.
Maybe we're the rain girls on the porch.
It's not great.
It's so sunny.
It looks like it's sunny.
Isn't it pretty amazing?
It's starting to rain like crazy.
My phone's dying.
It's pouring.
Ta-da!
It's terrible, isn't it?
It's amazing, isn't it?
The water is so powerful.
I'm looking forward to it.
Our tags are
It's falling.
Can you see it?
I don't know.
We've spontaneously gone to 100 points!
That's great!
It's low!
20?Twenty?
Twenty?
Twenty!
Oh, my God!
Here, here and here.
Oh, isn't that great?
Wow! That's great!
Please, please, please, please!
Now you're going to experience the surfing side,
Let's go for a drive first!
Thank you very much!
Yes!
Yes, OK! OK~!
First of all, I've got the first one!
I'm going to ask you to put the ball down,
On your left, put your right foot or your left foot, whichever is on top of here,
foot in front of you,
At first, it's hard to stand up,
so I'm going to hold it in my lap, and you're going to sit on it,
Center this.
Yes!
And then, you will hold it the same way you held it when you stood up earlier,
Bye bye!
You can hold this short.
It's not in the middle of the water, so keep it short.
Keep it short, and drop it slowly as you paddle left and right,
See how you feel the balance. Look at the sense of balance.
Oh~! I can stand up! Yeah!
I can stand up!
Yay! That's great!
Surprisingly, though,
You might be able to do it unexpectedly.
Hang in there! I'll do my best!
Oh, wow! This is fun!
Oh, my gosh! How did you get up?
That was fun!
Wow! Wow!
I'm equipped, take.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Wait!
You're scaring me!
Scary!
You're really tired when you equip it.
Whoa~! Wait!
The balance!
Oh no!
Oh, no! Are you okay?
A little bit!
Help me!
Wait a minute!
Is this what I think it is?
Oh, I got it.
Oh, no, I fell.
This is fun.
Oh, my God, Sol, you're doing it like a normal person.
I'm coming over there. I'm coming over there.
Sit down for a second. One time here.
Hey, Dad.
You want to go this way?
What's with the rock so close?
Can you climb it?
I can't.
Oh, I fell.
I can't go up there.
Sen-chan! Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Cute.
All right, let's go for it.
Amazing.
It's hard, isn't it? It's so hard to get up.
I can't.
You can do it. That's good.
You can do it.
It's hard to get around.
All right! Yeah!
I can stand up!
I think I should probably just face forward, you know?
Balance.
Feels good! I'm floating so high!
I'm having fun! It's fun! It's fun!
There's a stage over there too!
Maybe if I go a little further I can be a long distance racer on the sap!Maybe if I go a little further, I could be a long distance racer for Sapp.
If I put my mind to it.
I'm so happy!
I found my future dream, guys.
I'm going to be a sap.
Oh, I got a little mad when I said that.
I got a little angry.
That's funny.
What a funny way to fall.
What was that?
That broke my arm so bad!
You're a wanderer.
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Ooh!
Oh!
That feels good.
I like it.
It's fun.
It's good. It's great.
Fun.
It was fun.
I got to go in the ocean like normal.
It was a little salty.
It's a little salty.
Delicious.
Deliciously salty.Deliciously salty
I'm looking forward to it.
Anti-foods are definitely fun.
It's fun.
Cool.
Speed it up.
Oh, my God!
Oh, man!
It's fun!
Oh no!
Oh, man!
It's so much fun!
It's so much fun.
It's great.
Oh, my God.
So much fun.
Amazing.
Oh, my God.
Wow!
Whoo!
Yeah!
You're fast!That's fast!
Very fast!
It's totally different.
Wow!
Woah! That hurt!
That hurt too much!
No! That feels good!
Feels good!
Wow! That was fun!
That was fun!
Oh, yeah! Feels good!
Oh, man!
It's like a stress reliever! I know!
It feels so good!
That was great!
Yeah!
That was fun!
Let's go to the pool!
Yeah!
That's so cute.
I can take a really cute picture of this.
I think I need a few more.
So cute!
I saw a lot of autographs earlier.
I know, I know.
There's a lot of signatures in my stomach.
It's a bowl of katsu.It's a bowl of rice topped with a pork cutlet.
Yes, sir.
Oh, okay. This way, please.
Two chicken plates, please.
Thank you very much.
Bowl of katsu.
Looks delicious!
Is this what you call "food terrorism"?
Is it?
Looks delicious!
So cute!
Let's eat it while it's hot.
Yes, while it's still warm.
I'll put it in.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Do you want some cabbage?
Yes, please.
Wow, this is amazing.
This is absolutely delicious.
Can you order some on a plate?
Yes, thank you.
Order your plate, please.
Oh, it's so cute.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Yes, Saku-chan made it for me.
Mini tonkatsu-don!
This is the big one.This is the big one.
This is the mini one
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's great.
Wow.
Yum.
Mmm. - Mmm.
Delicious.
Yum.
I'm sorry to interrupt your meal, but...
This is my second trip to heaven.
Really?
Yes. I was hoping you could give me some advice.
I'm sure.
How's it going?
But in my case...
I have to talk all the time by myself.
I have to go to the store to get permission.
It's not easy.
But I've been able to make a few.
You don't have to worry about anything at all.
As long as you shoot normally, your good qualities will come out normally.
There's nothing to worry about at all.
You're cool.
Is he cool?
Your pace is totally different from usual.
That's true.
It's not as relaxed.
Today? Today?
I'm feeling much more active.
I'm more active when we're together.
When I'm alone.
I feel like I'm missing out on everything.
We all do.
I don't do anything at all.
Even on my days off.
I don't do anything.
That's right.
You don't have to do anything.
I'm alone.
I'll see you next time.
Slowly.
Thank you for dinner.
It was delicious.
It was good.
You're full.
I am.
Well, well, well... it's raining. It's raining today.
Well, I'm glad you were right, weatherman.
Well, well, well... bunny sports in the morning, you know, we've seen all kinds of weather today.
We've seen rainbows. Yeah, he said they're rare.
You know, a rainbow that low is really rare.
That's awesome! Yay!
You never know what's going to happen.
But it's almost the end of the show. But they said it's almost the end.
Yes, it's the end, but under such a dark umbrella.
This way, there's the ocean.
But I like it this way, too.
It's beautiful... even if I wanted to, I'd never be able to make something like this.
The tide is low and it's raining.
But it's okay... it's just an introduction.
The ocean has been through a lot.
Right, guys?
How was your trip to heaven? It was really fun.
Really? I'm glad.
Thank you very much. No, thank you very much.
Please watch the first three films.
If you haven't seen the first part, please watch the second part.
I'll be back. I'll be back.
It's been a pleasure.
So, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much. This is how it ends.
It's okay. It's okay.
See you later.
Bye, bye, bye.
This is fun!
That's great!
Subscribe to our channel!